<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael Balmes</title>
    <link>https://michaelbalmes.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Michael Balmes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://michaelbalmes.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Speech recognition needs versioning</title>
      <link>https://michaelbalmes.com/blog/voice-recognition-versioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelbalmes.com/blog/voice-recognition-versioning/</guid>
      <description>I feel betrayed. I let Amazon Alexa into my house and let her listen to all my amazing conversations that I have and all I ask is that she turns on the lights for me. But, now half the time I ask her to &amp;ldquo;turn on all my lights&amp;rdquo; she response &amp;ldquo;sorry, I didn&amp;rsquo;t find a device called northern lights&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;which one did you mean?&amp;rdquo; She used to work so amazing, but has gotten progressively worse over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serverless: still no such thing as a silver bullet</title>
      <link>https://michaelbalmes.com/blog/serverless/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelbalmes.com/blog/serverless/</guid>
      <description>Serverless is the new hotness right now, which means everyone is using it for everything and getting upset that isn&amp;rsquo;t some magical wand that solves all their problems. For example, cardgames.io switched from Elastic Beanstalk to Lambdas and saw their bills go up and response time get worse. But, isn&amp;rsquo;t the whole point of serverless that the built in autoscaling should save money and helps with performance?
When I talk about serverless, I tell people serverless is like Uber and everything else is like driving a car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://michaelbalmes.com/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelbalmes.com/me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Michael Balmes I like surronding myself with people smarter than me to make amazing software. I have a passion for cloud infrastructure, but I&amp;rsquo;m interested in all types of software. I believe in the principles of software craftmanship and building stable, tested software. I cut my teeth on the LAMP stack when I was 14 years old, but as an adult I like to write C#, JavaScript, and Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://michaelbalmes.com/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelbalmes.com/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>RAICS
RAICS is a multi-cloud distributed storage solution to increase privacy and security, provide extreme high-availability, and prevent vendor lock-in.
This Website
Built in hugo and hosted on Netlify.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>